When Bad Puppets Turn Good
Puppet Master 4 is a horror, science fiction,
fantasy film directed by Jeff Burr.
Blade, Tunneler, and Pinhead go toe-to-toe with a team of terrifying, gremlin-like creatures known as
"Totems" that are sent by the Egyptian demon Sutekh to recapture the magic stolen by Toulon.
Rick Myers, played by Gordon Currie.
Susie, played by Chandra West.
Cameron, played by Ash Adams.
Lauren, played by Teresa Hill.
Toulon, played by Guy Rolfe.
Dr. Carl Baker, played by Felton Perry.
Puppet Master (also titled The Puppet Master and Puppetmaster) is a 1989
American horror film written by Charles Band and Kenneth J.
Hall, and directed by David Schmoeller.
The film stars Paul Le Mat, Irene Miracle, Matt Roe and Kathryn O'Reilly as psychics who are
plotted against by a former colleague, using puppets animated by an Egyptian spell.
Originally intended for summer 1989 theatrical release, before being released on home video the following September, Puppet Master was ultimately pushed to
a direct-to-video release on October 12, 1989, as Band felt this was likely to be more financially successful than the theatrical market.
It was very popular and has since developed a large cult
following, and an extensive franchise.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.